mirrorcreator.com 2018-05-31

# Privacy Policy - Mirrorcreator.com - Upload Your files to multiple hosts

## Privacy Policy

**What data does Mirrorcreator store about the files I upload?**

* IP address of the computer from which the upload is started.
* Timestamp of the upload
* MD5 checksum of the uploaded file
* The file URL link entered by the uploader for remote uploads
* The e-mail address entered by the uploader

Data listed above may be shared with third party hosting sites you are uploading to as well. This may be required as part of their terms of service.

All files uploaded to our servers are stored temporarily for delivery and are deleted when they have been uploaded to third-party websites.

**Logging IP Addresses**

We automatically receive certain types of information when you interact with our Web pages, services and communications. This information includes your computer or digital device's IP address, access times, your browser type and language, type of operating system you use, your account activity and accessed pages. These information are logged and used by Mirrorcreator for measuring usage.

**Account Information**

We may ask for some personal information when you create an account, including, but not limited to, your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access. We also store the third party hosting account details you choose to enter in your account page. Any information you choose to provide should reflect how much you want others to know about you. You may review, update, correct or delete personal information or your account on your My Account page. In the event that Mirrorcreator is sold or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right to transfer or assign the information we have collected from you as part of any change of control.

**Certain Exceptional Disclosures**

We will not rent, sell or share your information with third parties. However, we may disclose your personal information or any of its log file information when we have a good faith belief that disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with a law, regulation or compulsory legal request; (b) co-operate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities; (c) identify persons who may be violating the law or legal notice; (d) protect and defend the rights or property of Mirrorcreator or third parties; (e) protect the safety of an individual or group; (f) prevent fraud or abuse of Mirrorcreator or its users.

**Use of Cookies**

We use "cookies" to collect information and improve our Services. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your digital device. We may use "persistent cookies" to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Service. We may use "session ID cookies" to enable certain features of the Service, to better understand how you interact with the Service and to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on the Service.

**Security of information**

The security of your information is important to us. We employ appropriate security measures in place to protect information collected from loss, destruction, disclosure, unauthorized access, misuse and alteration. Although we strive to protect your personal information, Mirrorcreator cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

**Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser.

**Your consent**

By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of these information by Mirrorcreator. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, contact us.

Last update: July 23, 2017
